{
  "listado": [
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "the new|york times",
      "pregunta": "1",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "facebook",
      "pregunta": "2",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "wordpress",
      "pregunta": "3",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "twitter",
      "pregunta": "4",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "chrome",
      "pregunta": "5",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "cartoon|network",
      "pregunta": "6",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "nickelodeon",
      "pregunta": "7",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "apple",
      "pregunta": "8",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "amazon",
      "pregunta": "9",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "whatsapp",
      "pregunta": "10",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "mini",
      "pregunta": "11",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "x box",
      "pregunta": "12",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "chevrolet",
      "pregunta": "13",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "ford",
      "pregunta": "14",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "kodak",
      "pregunta": "15",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "lacoste",
      "pregunta": "16",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "play|station",
      "pregunta": "17",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "peugeot",
      "pregunta": "18",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "mercedes|benz",
      "pregunta": "19",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "pepsi",
      "pregunta": "20",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "adidas",
      "pregunta": "21",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "fisher|price",
      "pregunta": "22",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "ferrari",
      "pregunta": "23",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "firefox",
      "pregunta": "24",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "nike",
      "pregunta": "25",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "levis",
      "pregunta": "26",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "volskwagen",
      "pregunta": "27",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "umbro",
      "pregunta": "28",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "coca cola",
      "pregunta": "29",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "bacardi",
      "pregunta": "30",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "motorola",
      "pregunta": "31",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "suzuki",
      "pregunta": "32",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "stella|artois",
      "pregunta": "33",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "shell",
      "pregunta": "34",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "seat",
      "pregunta": "35",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "samsung",
      "pregunta": "36",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "reebok",
      "pregunta": "37",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "telegram",
      "pregunta": "38",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "gucci",
      "pregunta": "39",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "converse",
      "pregunta": "40",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "fanta",
      "pregunta": "41",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "puma",
      "pregunta": "42",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "pritt",
      "pregunta": "43",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "audi",
      "pregunta": "44",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "mcdonalds",
      "pregunta": "45",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "chanel",
      "pregunta": "46",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "bridgestone",
      "pregunta": "47",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "bic",
      "pregunta": "48",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "carolina|herrera",
      "pregunta": "49",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "direct tv",
      "pregunta": "50",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "citroen",
      "pregunta": "51",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "instagram",
      "pregunta": "52",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "dodge",
      "pregunta": "53",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "speed",
      "pregunta": "54",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "louis|vuitton",
      "pregunta": "55",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "gatorade",
      "pregunta": "56",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "firestone",
      "pregunta": "57",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "quiksilver",
      "pregunta": "58",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "pinterest",
      "pregunta": "59",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "dove",
      "pregunta": "60",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "carrefour",
      "pregunta": "61",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "mitsubishi",
      "pregunta": "62",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "le coq|sportif",
      "pregunta": "63",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "opel",
      "pregunta": "64",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "linkedin",
      "pregunta": "65",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "nestle",
      "pregunta": "66",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "wilson",
      "pregunta": "67",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "pringles",
      "pregunta": "68",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "red bull",
      "pregunta": "69",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "lego",
      "pregunta": "70",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "honda",
      "pregunta": "71",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "minolta",
      "pregunta": "72",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "rip curl",
      "pregunta": "73",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "mizuno",
      "pregunta": "74",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "hewlett|packard",
      "pregunta": "75",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "starbucks",
      "pregunta": "76",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "giorgio|armani",
      "pregunta": "77",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "lotto",
      "pregunta": "78",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "new balance",
      "pregunta": "79",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "kappa",
      "pregunta": "80",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "rolex",
      "pregunta": "81",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "dropbox",
      "pregunta": "82",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "drive",
      "pregunta": "83",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "burger king",
      "pregunta": "84",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "timberland",
      "pregunta": "85",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "visa",
      "pregunta": "86",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "rayban",
      "pregunta": "87",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "opera",
      "pregunta": "88",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "vans",
      "pregunta": "89",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "intel",
      "pregunta": "90",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "wikipedia",
      "pregunta": "91",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "mercado libre",
      "pregunta": "92",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "ebay",
      "pregunta": "93",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "nbc",
      "pregunta": "94",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "pizza hut",
      "pregunta": "95",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "toyota",
      "pregunta": "96",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "bmw",
      "pregunta": "97",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "lg",
      "pregunta": "98",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "texaco",
      "pregunta": "99",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Logos",
      "respuesta": "national|geographic",
      "pregunta": "100",
      "categoria": "Logos"
    }
  ]
}
